<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">Obama’s re-election was a huge L for this nation.</statement>
     <statement id="2">If you thought Biden was bad, wait till Kamala or AOC get their turn.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Sadly, I honestly think a 6 hour Rogan podcast would be much better than partisan CNN/Fox shit now.</statement>
     <statement id="4">I'm solidly convinced that the only person Biden would have a chance against in '24 is Trump. Why? Because Trump pisses the left off THAT bad.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Biden, resume natural gas production in the US, and let the keystone pipeline be built. You’ll undo the damage at the pump and stop the hyperinflation.</statement>
     <statement id="6">Lol all politics aside and even taking into consideration the fact that Biden wanted a black woman as VP, there were literally multiple better qualified options who had already served in the Obama administration.</statement>
     <statement id="7">I hope that Biden does well for the same reason I hope the pilot flying my airplane does well.</statement>
     <statement id="8">Trump did a lot of good stuff but he spent four years trolling half the country and they came out and voted.</statement>
     <statement id="9">Ok, some Republicans are trash and so are some Democrats. Ok I'll say what I really mean, politicians aren't in it to help the population and it is annoying when people get all one sided about corruption as if it one side of the aisle does it.</statement>
     <statement id="10">I think most level headed people don't patriciate in hyperbole, partisanship and the art of politicizing every damn thing.</statement>
     <statement id="11">It's all political theater. If Trump would have won the election, you would have had democrats or whatever anti-Trump people saying "don't take Trump's vaccine."</statement>
     <statement id="12">The second amendment is a beautiful thing</statement>
     <statement id="13">Personally, I enjoy going to places I disagree with sometimes. It helps to get perspective and understand how others think. There are some things I disagree with but at the very least it helps me to understand how others view things.</statement>
     <statement id="14">An individuals right to speak freely should be upheld, regardless of platform.</statement>
     <statement id="15">The average person is not capable of complex, political style of thinking. They just care that The Bachelor is on at 8:00 tonight.</statement>
     <statement id="16">I hate woke culture so much.</statement>
     <statement id="17">This may not be the worst timeline, but it's definitely a shitty one. We all have to work together to change that. Let's put all these woke companies out of business.</statement>
     <statement id="18">Get rid of corporate donations and impose term limits. These two alone would clean up most of the swamp.</statement>
     <statement id="19">Maybe I’m naive, but I’ve been pretty shocked by just how little our government is willing to provide for our most basic human needs, such as food and shelter, during a global crisis. </statement>
     <statement id="20">The greatest tragedy of recent times is the inability to discuss ideals openly.</statement>
     <statement id="21">With democrats, personal responsibility is the last resort. For them, it’s all about being carried by society.</statement>
     <statement id="22">Remove politicians and the media from the picture and we'll find Americans have a heck of a lot in common. </statement>
     <statement id="23">Every piece of pro-vax propaganda paid some lip service to "talk to your doctor," pretending there would be an element of personal decision making and not just relentless browbeating into submission.</statement>
     <statement id="24">Time to get the entire country back to normal, full stop. Lift all restrictions, mandates, and emergency powers. The pandemic is over</statement>
     <statement id="25">i don't think any republican leaders support prohibiting masks. If you want to wear one, you're welcome to do what you want.</statement>
     <statement id="26">I've spoken with many who are just sick and tired of everything this pandemic and democrats have imposed on their lives.</statement>
     <statement id="27">I've heard stories of people not getting cancer treatments out of fear of catching COVID</statement>
     <statement id="28">Nobody has ever said you should be forced to take it. But private companies have the freedom to only accept vaccinated customers</statement>
     <statement id="29">It's not some gubment conspiracy, vaccines are keeping people from being hospitalized.</statement>
     <statement id="30">I strongly recommend people check with their doctor and get the shot. You don’t want Covid. It sucks.</statement>
     <statement id="31">The vaccines clearly help save lives and hospital resources.</statement>
     <statement id="32">A month or two before the elections we’ll find ourselves in the midst of another outbreak that causes us to have to shut down again and only vote by mail so that the Democrats still manage to “win.”</statement>
     <statement id="33">Fwiw I'm pro vaccine and anti mandate.</statement>
   </statements>